okay thank you when you think about the
first time you we met what do you
remember
thank you I remember I thought you I
thought you were the younger brother I
thought you were David yeah you thought
I was white yeah that was that you
tricked me a lot there I remember and
you had a skateboard too you escaped
down my walk I remember you said that it
was that I'll pass by your house and I
looked at your house you did you looked
up at the window I thought you saw me I
wanted to kick your ass in karate
what you couldn't yeah we you went up to
me the next day I remember you were like
and when we met cuz we grappled that day
did they befriend a grapple yeah it was
a horrible graduation
you remember sensei guy - yeah I
remember this is sloppy
Oh 16 you were six you were a sophomore
I was house what have you seen here
anything
yeah because I might you know it was a
year later then we started going on no
yeah I got left back once I was a
freshman I believe you were certainly
refreshing yours at Union what do you
love about our relationship I love about
we make our own silly jokes yeah we
always quote spongebob she's gonna say
that all right I told my friends I love
that we can I can mention any line a
movie and we just start cracking up yes
as we know where it's from
well I need to pick it up cuz you always
you always do quotes on the phone movie
yeah you started it with your cousin and
then I got used to it I love that were
lazy I don't mind being home with you I
don't want you doing
no at least once a month we had to do
something yeah
I don't like being at home you know at
least we did together mm-hmm
and we live one block apart from each
other yeah
know your old bed frame you know you
like that
we used to write oh yeah I remember
yeah that was all your old childhood
moments yeah
how are you wrote your name well you
wrote chef's reading oh do they call you
that in high school
mm-hmm I gave you that developed are you
yeah I'm surprised did I keep yeah oh
did you know I kept it I kept it
I kept it was it what they were your
friends did well oh my god because you
hadn't delivered to the high school no
we go a Pizza Hut yes right once a year
damn lunch on when do you feel closest
to me those jokes on my friend you know
I feel closer with you when when you're
on your laptop and you know and I'm on
my thing you know like I'm just like
play video games you know even though
we're doing our you know separate thing
you know we always have time to make to
come together for at least one minute or
two minutes and then you know we go back
to our thing you know we take another 30
minute break then we go back together
that's why like that's that's that
that's the time we feel closest together
because you know you see something you
know even though we're together in the
same house you know we you know we leave
us you know we just leave we just do
what we gotta do yeah but then we know
we just for two minutes we come back
together it might not have you know all
these sort of jokes yeah imagine I was
on top of you all the time
turn off your video game and stuff I
don't know imagine if I was like that oh
oh yeah yeah yeah would you like that
no that was I think yeah I don't know I
wouldn't like that I don't
[Music]
what are you hesitant to tell me well
I'm not hesitant remember I said I
didn't say I love you because I don't
believe in love that much yeah with my
family but then you know like I got used
to it you know since we've been together
for six years you know I come closer
closer to me you say yes I say a little
bit more now you used to get mad and
I'll say it but I used to show it to you
but I don't say it to you
because it made no sense I would tell
you just say it just say it what's the
problem no it's not that big a deal it's
not we've been together for so long no
but it's nice to hear once in a while I
don't mind hearing oh you know I can't
have me say it how is it to you before
you go to sleep my kiss either night
sometimes I don't know everything cuz
I'm not I pretty much saw you at
everything but I can't worry other
person I'd dump everything on because of
my friends like Dallas and Georgina and
like all those people like they they
hear the other side of it no you used to
be hesitant for some stuff and while you
didn't tell everything one day like like
though the time that you went to the
hospital you know cuz you always because
you felt alone you know I don't know you
just wanted to end it there
it took you like what like two years I
mean and the time you said that sense8
letter he sent it to you oh yeah
that was like what I was like oh
those before we started on out when that
happened that I gave me like a huge shot
yeah forget about it that's good that
you forgot yeah yeah no we're not has a
lioness feels good all right tell me
about the time I just bought
disappointed you and how do you feel
about it now oh my god how I feel about
it now I'm so over it with a mini
program
well I took like I don't like like three
days yeah I I don't know like once I
couldn't like I said no remember I told
you I couldn't I couldn't sleep like I
feel like I felt weird like I felt like
something came up you know like
something I'm missing something
yeah and then I realized that you know
maybe you're the man that I was meant to
be with think I do not like that anymore
no I'm actually happy not like I was
confused back then yeah you cuz you're
so young yeah yeah but we've been
together for two years I was in the
second year mm-hmm
yeah I guess we should tell her you know
like you don't want to be within the
same relationship but so long
you know you wanted to explore it but
that's what's getting me confused but
they know of your lies I don't have to
be everyone else that's crazy because my
friends are exploring now like yeah well
if you see the way they they want a
relationship
yeah like the entire exploring
especially Dallas it's time takes time
[Music]
do we have enough sex why do we have
enough sex yes yes once a week there's
one Saturdays I think it's good when we
first thought it was a lot you remember
mm-hmm all right
no no no no it was the first time both
of us yeah I thought that was a good
thing I think it feels good having it at
least once a week yeah of course yeah
without the pressure that we have until
we move out at least yep
oh okay am I the best sex you ever had
yeah but I think personally yeah yeah we
- we don't you know we always spice it
up trying something new
okay what is the act you'd like to try
put our afraid to ask what is the act
you like to try that act act but you
want to try but you're afraid to ask me
in a sexual way I don't think we ever
I'm not questioning what do you think
yeah well I want to see how it is to
like live good you know yeah we we sleep
over but we don't yeah I want to see how
that okay yeah I mean I know I had to
cut yeah sometimes clean you I don't
mind being a housewife do you everything
about other people during sex
whoo no no no me I think when we first
started yeah yeah but then they got away
went away yeah I don't know no I guess
that was young it was what every guy no
dirty sex
I'd like I wonder how other people have
sex no not when we having sex not like I
sunshine think no yeah Oh like friends
yeah like like your friends especially
yeah definitely it's so weird specially
when they start talking about it they're
always talking about it you know when we
have our late nights
yeah you guys spring up sex and I just
think quiet cuz it'll piss off though
they haven't had in a wife okay
those part of you feel like you're
missing out by being with me for so long
you feel like you miss you know I feel
like I'm missing out with I don't know
probably like like exploring or like
going out of town
like I couldn't went to Rhode Island you
know we weren't together like but then I
realized like I want to be with you you
can't force you to stay no yeah you can
go there was a decision between me so
yeah yeah sometime when I heard of how I
would have been like if I was a Rhode
Island where I have to sing you know
type of I get down with the scared I
have right now with you or like back
then cuz I need I not help back then and
you know you helped me
do you think it would have al do you
even fail no but I think I would have
like fucking lost concentration
probably yeah anything you what a party
a lot I think so yeah I think that's one
thing to like I want to experience a
college party
Oh like by yourself right yeah you know
with my friends yeah you know like doing
friends know their college friends do
you wanna go visit a weekend women like
you want to go visit them for a weekend
I wanted to yeah but no I don't you I
don't know like I said it's a long way
to I mean yeah most of my friends is in
you or dying actually Darren Johnson
Wales right yeah some of them they're
still there how many years that you have
a year left
yeah well basically yeah that's crazy I
know
I personally don't feel like I'm gonna
see now um everything I do I was include
you know no matter what no matter what I
know if I want to travel I will travel
with you problem I never feel like oh my
god I miss you now cuz I I don't I feel
like I can handle it I can handle ball I
can balance both I learn how to do that
yeah I learn to do that now - yeah I
mean it's hard sometimes when I want to
stay late and you know I have to say
late and then you know I have to doctor
come home you know I don't mind yeah
sometimes no yeah you know what I do my
actually what that I realize is you're
doing it for your work
yeah I don't it's a party or anything
yeah what's your fantasy that we have to
try again
and why heavily yeah well any type of
fantasy that's not sexual fantasy I
wanted to travel like a road trip
I honestly that's what you want to do
yeah and like go to different food
places oh my god then we watch the Food
Channel
Dinah - well nothing wrong there was a
fool
yeah members his food yeah not bizarre
for what's good that's only members are
from the last class but you like a road
trip
yeah I like to follow you know my father
sent them for like other other countries
other countries yeah like what garam I
know maybe on Asia
oh yeah of course
Japan Japan you know I'm always into
those yeah Asian stuff Asian culture
yeah yeah
freaking out of me
is that really your fantasy though why
that was mine no one else another
fantasy actually I want to go to like a
like a Blizzcon you know like those oh
yeah it's for real things yeah or et
game
yeah you know what let's call yeah III
right is it 83 I don't know you know all
the games comes out in June you could
experience it that's all I want to do
that's enough Nancy don't I sound a
little comic-con with you okay it's fun
I like comic-con I go there for the
video game stuff I don't go there for
the book for the comments for the comics
yet but the costumes are awesome when it
should dress up oh my god okay yes that
one right okay do I still turn you all
the way I did when we first met I think
you turn me on now more yeah you turned
out more now than back then like I said
back then I used to think about other
people or not just not just thinking
about you know I know you're I know your
favorite spots yeah you still turn me on
- yes are we
and we broke up and got back together I
was exactly like the first time I didn't
touch team like three days when we first
kissed again after we come back together
yeah in your room yeah what was that
whatever cuz you know me so well do you
think I'm the one for you yes yeah yeah
I think we always meant for each other I
think that's one thing yeah that's what
I was confused at first like like I feel
like wow I did I already found the
person I want to be with like I was just
like like I want to explore further and
then later on you know but you know what
I guess I found the person already
I don't why is that
yeah because we now we gave I could
expand as new inventory's with another
person which is good that's fine
hey my friends complain about how single
they are like it's good for them to be
single you know for the life that they
want like georgina wants to travel so
that's all you have to be single now you
know well the kind of trap I don't see
there balancing stuff but like the house
what's a relationship like this like
long time yeah it's it's rare for this
actually especially a young age yeah
that's right
that's like an accomplishment actually
and achievement
[Music]
when was the last time you almost
cheated on me probably talking you know
no cheated but I know if it went any
further than yeah I haven't physically
cheating with another person like not
like touching anything like that but I
think I was doing the time that's all
it's that cotechino oh yes absolutely
okay I see Mildred going through it babe
and I can't I can't
she's going through right now yeah I
heard you for like an hour
what's the biggest compromise you've
made that I haven't acknowledged I think
I think you know all my compromises like
sometimes I won't stay late to my work
and I really want to but I want to stay
with you as well like that's the risk
I'm taking
yeah like I say I got in like a photo
job like I don't know the country I
would go you'll go yeah because I know
you understand yeah yeah I wasn't yeah
like if it's for a week or I just like
if you've got the same thing I was yeah
I want to say well again there is this
everyone get nervous but don't know and
sounds pretty great good you know it's
what you want to do I mean I would do
the same thing most of things you know
the thing that I want to do is probably
in Canada anyways oh yeah oh yeah
Washington if I want to know one thing
Washington like following the west coast
see ya know Seattle yeah
do you thought you compromised like your
freedom or something normalizes like you
know yeah no actually no not yet
oh yeah
[Music]
yeah I mean you know next year it's kind
of something new what's gonna happen if
everything goes well did you did you ask
oh yeah
who has more power than religion you are
weak don't know
no I think we shared up how I feel like
you have more in anymore you think so no
I like your tone hey don't do that or
like hey don't drink too much or no you
know they give me a call every time
you're out yeah like yeah you know I'm
probably do I feel like we share the
power but I think so too
you know you sometimes want to be a mom
towards me so yeah I have more power to
me too
no no name one thing okay
[Laughter]
you used to come when I go on eleven and
the worst neighborhood yeah yeah I know
especially j-train this yeah no but I
was fine even died also worried too
I mean it's a big difference before man
and a female and not experienced
something going traveling alone actually
a night
yeah you know same same thing could
happen for both of us love like there's
more percentage than something to happen
to you that's about it
if you could change one thing and our
relationship what would it be and why
the fuck out that's one thing that would
change yeah between us
oh think so you guys so far all that
shit and the first three years are the
worst yeah I think the first thing yeah
we're over right we're over it no
seriously I just think like we're like I
tell people you're my best friend so
that's the only thing I would change
I just I want us to just keep moving on
with our life I don't want us to stay
there and fucking Jamaica Queens until
we're 36 yeah no I can't wait till you
drive
I'm getting there yeah I'm so happy
why'd you change anything between us at
least mm-hmm I don't know I can't answer
I could I don't know yeah more sex I'm
staring cos no we live we're on a fire
scene we don't have I was here we
doesn't it's gonna take time you know
it's time no we had to wait moving out
was the best solution action I think so
too I hope so was the last one was a you
yeah thank no wait thank you you picked
this one over
yeah I'll get the last one oh do you
want to marry me all right now I can't
yeah I can see I was thinking about it
but I can't not not now I was sad with
my family five 10 years and I want dirty
okay when we have a life together
already
I think so too you know like we've done
with school and we we've already found
our careers yeah I would definitely
marry you though yeah me too
yep just like your grandma grandpa
they met when they were really young -
there are my parents I think we met
younger I think we were young and they
meant like no 19 20
I got married a fucking 18 though it's
crazy
my parents got married at 23 yeah I'm
right now mm-hmm
oh yeah yeah we'll marry you but not no
no I said I will take your last name yes
I thought that was her last name and he
was like he's like I don't like it
yeah oh oh please would you hate me why
did you dress me no no I mean like
everyone's doing that now I have a -
yeah they do but I can't what other
fucking - away how did you feel about
this that is normal it's normal
conversation yeah yeah I don't mind that
Oh actually actually want to do this
more accident really
oh good I thought you'd be nervous over
Nina no that's okay I'm still really
worried about my car though no that's
fine you sure yeah beside about the
money now oh yeah you have a question
yeah question is how would how can you
see us and finally the next do you see
they see the they'll see us together yes
like you you don't see any type of
myself I think in the future when living
together I feel like the other might be
a situation the only thing I would worry
about yeah it's already bills and stuff
like that also financially I financially
yeah yeah just I don't want to fight
about that shit I really don't know cuz
the odd isn't my parents I don't like
that sending my parents yeah I hate that
shit mm-hmm yeah the funny thing is I
don't see us getting like pregnant or
anything till way later on I don't see
that yeah cuz that could happen no I'm
not actually
absolutely couldn't handle that that's
pregnancy's I wasn't back of my mind
actually explode yeah as long as we
could see us together next you know five
years or so do you do you really think
you're gonna be in games aside I don't
know you know I'm always changing you
know you are but like I feel like yeah
you know I think that was my true
destiny for fun the longest I always
wanted to do something with the video
games yeah I want you to I don't want
you and they don't work in a restaurant
at all or a retail store like for in
your life don't know yeah yeah I can do
that I'm throwing that I shouldn't
let you know anything put that well what
we do event that I am that I don't know
well I still push you to go yeah
seriously